As I have said, and I publicly said on
July 1st that the second half of midterm
years historically is the accumulation
window. It's hard to nail down the exact
low. What's interesting is that so far
that low occurred so far on July 1st,
the very first day of the second half of
the midterm year. But if you guys
remember when the bull market was still,
you know, back in 2025 when it first
really started to look like we were
entering into the bear market, what I
said back then that you know, we thought
it was a bear market already. But then
the final nail in the coffin for the
bull market was the weekly close below
the 50-week moving average. If you go
back and look throughout all prior bull
markets, once you're below the 50-week
moving average, it's over, right? Like
it's always been over when Bitcoin
dropped below the 50-week. The bull
market has always been over. No matter
how much people tried to manifest the
bull market back, it was always over on
two weekly closes